so inspections you can see that you know
这样检查就可以知道
one of the things that IntelliJ does is
IntelliJ做的一件事是
tell you a warning about all of these
告诉你所有这些警告
different types of inspections that you
您所进行的不同类型的检查
have and if you go to inspections here
有，如果你去这里检查
and if you know how to type you see that
如果您知道如何键入，您会看到
we have a whole bunch of different
我们有一堆不同的东西
inspections and you can switch these on
检查，您可以将其打开
and off a lot of times when people come
人们来的时候很多次
to IntelliJ they like stop babysitting
去IntelliJ他们喜欢停止保姆
me stop telling me this shouldn't be
我停止告诉我这不应该
done oh that shouldn't be done I like my
完成了哦，不应该这样做，我喜欢我的
coat to throw in all exceptions right so
大衣可以抛出所有异常
you can switch these off and you can
您可以将其关闭，然后
customize them and you can adapt them to
自定义它们，您可以使它们适应
different projects and you can add to
不同的项目，您可以添加到
these obviously as well you can add to
这些显然也可以添加到
these in in you know creating plugins
这些在您知道创建插件
and I'll show you in a different way now
我将以另一种方式向您展示
as well but basically all of these you
同样，但基本上所有这些你
can switch on and off you can set the
可以打开和关闭，您可以设置
severity level you can define the scope
您可以定义严重性级别的范围
where it's applicable etc and these now
适用的地方等等，这些现在
show up individually here if you
如果您单独出现在这里
right-click and select go to next
右键单击并选择转到下一步
problem it will show you all the hints
问题，它将为您显示所有提示
tips suggestions etc if you just say
提示建议等，如果您只是说
high-priority problems it will only
高优先级的问题只会
navigate to the next actual error what
导航到下一个实际错误
IntelliJ considers an error so when you
IntelliJ认为错误，所以当您
use the the next highlighted arrow next
使用下一个突出显示的下一个箭头
previous highlighted error that will
先前突出显示的错误将
only go through errors it won't go
只经历错误而不会经历
through suggestion hints etc so here
通过建议提示等，所以在这里
there's a couple of other kind of like
还有另外两种
interesting things that you can do if I
如果我可以做一些有趣的事情
go for example to comparison failure and
例如比较失败和
I select expected there's an analyze
我选择期望有一个分析
menu which I found in a lot of people
我在很多人中发现的菜单
don't use and there is analyze data flow
不使用并且有分析数据流
to here and from here and basically what
到这里，从这里到基本上
that is saying to you is analyzing where
就是说你正在分析哪里
the variables are being read where the
读取变量的地方
variable that you're on is being set
您正在设置的变量
whether it's for a method whether it's
是否用于方法是否
for property whether it's for a variable
对于属性，是否用于变量
it analyzes that for you and shows you
它为您分析并向您显示
all of the different places where this
在所有不同的地方
is being read and being set and that's
正在被读取和设置，这是
very good to kind of understand the flow
非常了解这种流程
that's going on so we also have support
正在进行中，所以我们也有支持
for basically sequel stuff I'm not
基本上是续集，我不是
judging anyone for putting sequel
评判是否有续集
statements in strings right so let's
正确的字符串语句，所以让我们
just put that aside and pretend we're
只是把它放在一边，假装我们
not talking about that but if you do
不是在说那个，但如果你这样做
these kind of things there is completion
这些事情有完成
you can get all of that hooked up
你可以把所有的东西都连接起来
and you can basically come here and help
你基本上可以来这里帮忙
to enter and say run query in console so
输入并说在控制台中运行查询，以便
you get all of this information here so
您在这里获得所有这些信息，因此
you know we provide good support and if
您知道我们会提供良好的支持，如果
I click here and say controls f6
我点击这里说控制f6
renamed to not a resource you can get
重命名为无法获得的资源
basically compactor across your entire
基本上压实整个
code base and across the database okay
代码库和整个数据库都可以
so use the built in tools that we
因此，使用我们内置的工具
provide for that kind of support with
提供这样的支持
databases okay
数据库还可以
working with version control some quick
快速使用版本控制
tips and tricks there how many of you
那里的技巧和窍门
use git the majority of people use git
使用git大多数人使用git
right so we support all of the different
对，所以我们支持所有不同的
version controls but if you come here
版本控制，但如果您来这里
and select the version control you can
然后选择您可以的版本控制
see that you have a log and it
看到你有一个日志，它
represents all of the different
代表所有不同
check-ins etc I'm using git here you can
签到等我在这里使用git
select two different things press
选择两个不同的东西按
control D and see differences on those
对照D并查看其中的差异
two commits you can actually also for
您实际上还可以进行两次提交
instance if you switch on annotate you
实例，如果您打开注释您
get annotations of who made changes etc
获取谁进行更改的注释等
here so I can bring this down and let's
在这里，我可以把它放下来，让我们
say for instance I come here and that's
比如说我来这里，那是
a annotation here I can right click here
我可以在这里右键单击注释
and say copy revision number and then
然后说出修订版本号，然后
select our revision number put it here
选择我们的修订号放在这里
and it will show me that exact revision
它会告诉我确切的修订
number in the in the actual log right
实际日志右边的数字
eye and you can say I'm biased or what I
眼睛，你可以说我有偏见或我有什么
I came from visual studio I was really
我来自视觉工作室，当时我真的
reluctant to using integration inside
不愿在内部使用集成
tools for many years I refused to do it
工具很多年我拒绝这样做
with IntelliJ I kept dropping back to
与IntelliJ我一直回落到
the command line but at some point I
命令行，但在某些时候我
picked it up and I have to say that in
捡起来，我不得不说
in general I'm pleased with it
总的来说，我很满意
you have all of the commits message box
您拥有所有的提交消息框
so for example I can come here and say
所以例如我可以来这里说
random nonsense and then hit commit here
随意胡说八道，然后点击此处提交
you can do like you know the commit you
你可以做的就像你知道提交
can run reform are called rearrange code
可以进行改革的称为重排代码
optimizer imports do all of the code
优化程序导入会执行所有代码
analysis check to do et cetera do
做分析检查等等
uploads all of these things and then you
上传所有这些东西，然后您
can do a commit and push create
可以进行提交并推动创建
Hach etc so all of this is possible you
哈希等，所以所有这些都是可能的
can we've even added the feature that
我们甚至可以添加功能
during the commit you can do a diff and
在提交期间，您可以进行比较和
during the diff diff you can even edit
在diff diff期间，您甚至可以进行编辑
the files without having to switch out
无需切换文件
of the context of that dialog directly
该对话框的上下文
in that dialog to do editing then of
在该对话框中进行编辑
course with the with the log here you
当然，这里有日志
can we also have support for
我们也可以支持
cherry-picking and a whole bunch of
采摘樱桃和一大堆
things but this is kind of specific to
事情，但这是特定于
get so I don't want to delve too much
得到，所以我不想钻太多
into that so here I have Java 8
到这里，所以我有Java 8
lots of lambdas looks beautiful in five
五个中的许多lambda看起来很漂亮
years we'll be maintaining that stuff
几年，我们将维护这些东西
and I've got a list of people etc so if
而且我有一个人名单等等，如果
I set for instance a breakpoint here and
我在这里设置了一个断点，
if I hit debug well you know what's
如果我很好地调试，你知道是什么
gonna happen but before I do that right
会发生，但是在我做对之前
click here how many of you have ever
点击这里你们有多少人
right clicked on that okay and clicked
右键单击，然后单击
on more substantially few um so if you
在几微米上，所以如果你
click on more you get a whole bunch of
点击更多，你会得到一大堆
options so you can like set up break
选项，以便您可以设置休息时间
point conditionally you can log messages
点有条件，您可以记录消息
to console.log evaluated expressions you
用console.log计算表达式
know all of these different things you
知道所有这些不同的事情
can create groups of breakpoints enable
可以创建断点组启用
those breakpoints and a group level
这些断点和组级别
disable them in a group level a whole
整体禁用他们在组级别
bunch of different things that you can
一堆不同的东西，你可以
do there then what you can also do is if
在那里做，那么你也可以做的是
I come here and see if I set a
我来这里看看是否设置了
breakpoint we've got a new feature it
断点，我们有一个新功能
says what do you want to break on do you
说你想打破什么吗
want to break on the entire line or do
想在整条线上休息或做
you want to break on individual lambda
你想打破个人lambda
expressions there and you can actually
表达在那里，你实际上可以
come here as well and do run and debug
也来这里做运行和调试
right we've got the little gutter thing
是的，我们有小东西
so if you hit gutter here and I start to
所以如果你在这里打水槽，我开始
debug you can see that it D bugs
调试您可以看到它是D bug
everything if I do a step into I'm
一切，只要我迈出一步
stepping into the different lambdas
跨入不同的lambda
right we also have I'm not going to show
好的，我们也不会显示
but you also can now fully do evaluation
但您现在也可以完全进行评估
of lambda expressions with code
代码的lambda表达式集
completion when you do evaluate
完成评估时
expression you know you get all of the
表达你知道你得到所有
code completion anything you can
代码补全
anything you want there and list of
您想要的任何东西和清单
people you get all of that you can even
人们得到的一切，你甚至可以
evaluate lambda expressions there so use
在那里评估lambda表达式，因此使用
some of those features that that we
我们所拥有的一些功能
provide we do have some tools if your
提供我们有一些工具，如果您
die hard terminal
硬终端
person you can get terminal alt F 12 you
你可以得到终端ALT F 12的人
can not have multiple tabs in the
中不能有多个标签
terminal so all of that is there a lot
终端，所以这一切都很多
of times you've noticed that I've used
有时您已经注意到我已经使用过
this keyboard combination shift command
此键盘组合移位命令
a remember that one right that is when
记住，那是当
you don't know the keyboard binding for
你不知道键盘绑定
something you can look it up by name so
您可以通过名称查找它，以便
rename and it will invoke it it's
重命名，它将调用它
basically a action lookup and it also
基本上是一个动作查找
sometimes says the the quick shortcut
有时会说快速捷径
key for it so for example refactor you
它的关键，例如重构
can see that it shows you the keyboard
可以看到它显示了键盘
shortcut for it so it's a good way to
它的捷径，所以这是一个很好的方法
look things up and also if you don't
查找事物，如果您不查找
remember it just do it so I say for
记得做就做，所以我说
example structurally search and I invoke
结构搜索示例，我调用
structure research okay and there's this
结构研究好了，有这个
other thing here which I promise you
我答应你的另一件事
that probably no one has ever gone to
可能没有人去
which is called I don't even know what
被称为我什至不知道是什么
it's called yeah productivity guide how
这就是所谓的生产力指南
many of you have seen that right you
你们中许多人都看到了
probably imagine it's gonna go to a
可能想象它会去
website no it opens up a dialog box that
网站否，它会打开一个对话框，
shows you a lot of the things that I've
向您展示了我所拥有的很多东西
been showing you and it also tells you
一直在向你展示，它还告诉你
how many times you've used it and when
您使用了多少次，何时使用
you last used it right so for instance I
您上次使用正确，例如
can come here and say 79 smart type
可以来这里说79智能型
completion it explains to you what that
完成它向您说明
is it shows you how to use it it tells
它告诉您如何使用它告诉您
you when you used it and when you last
您何时使用它以及何时使用
use it okay
好好用
so with that we're more or less done
因此，我们或多或少地完成了
time is up as it says here
时间到了，就像这里所说的